CONTACT

(2)

0976060432

 \bowtie

tuanitpro@gmail.com

http://tuanitpro.com

06, Hoa Cúc, Phú Nhuận Hồ Chí Mih City

SOCIAL

in tuanitpro



tuanipro



tuanitpro



tuanitpro



tuanitpro

KEY ACHIEVEMENT

Good knowledge of C#-OOP, HTML, ASP/ASP.NET MVC, WPF and Windows Form Application, database programming language.

Good knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ajax Angular JS, Typescript (object oriented with JavaScript, HTML standard compliance, HTM5/CSS3)

Good knowledge of .NET Framework (C#/VB.NET), OOP Design Principles

Good knowledge of Windows Services, WCF/Web Service/ASP.NET Web APIs, .NET Core

Lê Thanh Tuấn

.NET Developer

PERSONAL STATEMENT

With over 5 years working as a developer with Microsoft platform, also in charge of some positions from analyzing to developing, deploying system, I have a deep understanding about software architecture which enables me to learn new technology fast and easily.

I also can work under pressure and have strong passion for learning new things

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER

2010-present

Developer/Team Leader

MAIN RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Meeting with clients to gather the requirements.
- Designing the system flow & architecture, database schema...
- Planning task & set project minestones & goals.
- Work as developer.
- Support team member to finish tasks.
- Solving problems when needed.
- Making tests.

ACHIEVEMENTS AND SKILLS GAINED:

- Improve team leading skill.
- Improve task management skill.
- Improve requirement gathering skill.
- Improve develop/programming skill

SEO Application (Auto SEO)

Jan 2018-May 2018

Gia Khánh Land, Company

ABOUT PROIECT:

SEO Application (Auto SEO) / Application support for SEOer.

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES: C#, Entity Framework, SQL Lite

TEAM WITH 2 MEMBERS

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY:

- Business Analyst / Main Developer
- Communicating with clients/departments & deriving requirements.
- Define business flow.
- Meeting with project manager to define milestone & release schedule.

SKILLS

→ Full stack.

Software Development, Architecture software, OS, Database

→ C#, Backend

Half of my projects are working with C# Winform, NET Framework, WPF..

\rightarrow .Net MVC, .NET Core, API

Over 5 years with C#, I'm very familiar with this and can handle a project from nothing to release

ightarrow DESIGN PATTERN, DI/IOC, ORM

Good knowledge of Desing Pattern and apply to project, Good knowledge of ORM: EF, BLToolkit, Dapper

\rightarrow Front end

HTM5, CSS3, Javascript, AngularJs, Angular 5, Typescript

ightarrow Open Source

NopeCommerce.., Open source platform for builder app

- → CRITIAL THIKING, OPEN-MINDED
- \rightarrow COMMUNICATION

\rightarrow RESEARCH SKILL

I also can work under pressure and have strong passion for learning new things

EDUCATION

DALAT UNIVERSITY 2007

2012

IT Engineer Information Technology

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Reading
- Coding
- Sport
- Music

WORK EXPERIENCE (continued)

QUIZZ APPLICATION

Ian 2018 - May 2018

Main Developer Build on deman

ABOUT PROJECT:

Quizz Application Online for IT Faculty of University Dalat

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

.NET Core, Angular 5. SQL Server, Entity Framework

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY

- Work as Business Analyst and Project Manager.
- Research and support technical team.
- Define business flow.
- Design database architecture..
- Solve problems when needed.
- Planning, scheduling & testing.
- Deploy system to clients

CRYPTOCURENCY EXCHANGE

Oct 2017 - Dec 2017

Team Member, Developer Build on deman ABOUT PROJECT:

Internal Crypto Currency Exchange Platform

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

C#, .Net Mvc, Entity Framework, SignalR, Realtime, Crypto API

TEAM WITH 5 MEMBERS

MAIN RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Team member Developer
- Communicating with clients/departments & deriving requirements.
- Define business flow.
- Coding
- Meeting with project manager to define milestone & release schedule.

RECOGNITION AND GAINS:

- Improve business analyzing skill.
- Develop teamwork spirit.

WORK EXPERIENCE (continued)

HRM SOLUTION

Iun 2017 - Sep 2017

Team Member, Developer

ABOUT PROJECT:

Maintainent for currently project of Customer, Develope new feature

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

.NET MVC, Angular 5. SQL Server, Entity Framework

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY

- Team member
- Research and support technical team.
- Coding review
- Solve problems when needed.

SCG CRM

May 2017 - Sep 2017

Team Member, Developer Build on deman

ABOUT PROJECT:

Microsite, CMR for SCG

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

C#, .Net Mvc Entity Framework, SignalR

TEAM WITH 5 MEMBERS

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY

- Team member Developer
- Communicating with clients/departments & deriving requirements.
- Define business flow.
- Coding
- Meeting with project manager to define milestone & release schedule.

SALES MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

May 2016 - Jul 2016

Business Analyst, Main Developer

ABOUT PROJECT:

Track sales and reward points, ROI tracking, KPI tracking

Sales performance management, SMS marketing

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

.NET MVC, SignalR, Realtime, SMS API. SQL Server, Entity Framework

TEAM WITH 2 MEMBERS

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY

- Business Analyst, Main Developer, Research and support technical
 team
- Solve problems when needed.
- Communicating with clients/departments & deriving requirements.

UPQUES SOCICAL NETWORKING

2015

Business Analyst, Developer

ABOUT PROJECT:

Social sharing knowledge, Platform quora.com Startup

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

C#, .Net Mvc Entity Framework, MongoDB, SignalR, Facebook, Socical API

TEAM WITH 2 MEMBERS

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY

- Define business flow.
- Coding Review
- Develope
- Deploy

YERSIN UNIVERSITY WEBSITE CMS May 2015 – Oct 2015

Business Analyst, Main Developer

ABOUT PROJECT:

Webiste to show activities of Yersin University

Management news, student information, timesheets & transcript inside university

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

.NET MVC, SignalR, SQL Server, Entity Framework, Angular Js. Jquery

TEAM WITH 2 MEMBERS

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY

- Business Analyst, Main Developer
- Research and support technical team.
- Coding review
- Solve problems when needed.
- Communicating with clients/departments & deriving requirements.
- Define business flow.

STUDENT HOUSING MANAGEMENT Mar 2015 – Jun 2015 **SYSTEM**

Business Analyst, Main Developer

ABOUT PROJECT:

Build for Dormitory of Dalat University

Management Student Information, Student finacicals, Student Activities

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

C#, .Net Mvc Entity Framework, SQL Server, Jquery

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY

- Define business flow.
- Coding, Coding Review
- Deploy system to clients.

WORK EXPERIENCE (continued)

BID AUCTION SYSTEM

Jul 2014 – Otc 2014

Business Analyst, Main Developer

ABOUT PROJECT:

Website Ecommerce, Inculde bid auction

PLATFORM & TECHNIQUES:

.NET MVC, SignalR, Realtime SQL Server, Entity Framework, Angular Js. Jquery

ROLE & RESPONSIBILITY

- Business Analyst, Main Developer
- Research and support technical team.
- Coding review
- Solve problems when needed.
- Communicating with clients/departments & deriving requirements.
- Define business flow.
- Deploy system to clients.

More project

Find more project at http://github.com/tuanitpro

